eden-court.co.uk 2013-05-19

# Privacy Policy | Eden Court

Eden Court Highlands is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

You can browse our website without disclosing any personal information, however if you register for our online booking service, mailing list, email bulletins or provide personal data in any other form, we will only process your personal data in accordance with the relevant legislation.

**Security**

All information is received by us and retrieved using secure technology. In order to provide a safe and secure environment for your personal information we use up to date technology with a view to protecting that information against loss, misuse or unauthorised alteration. We only allow authorised personnel access to personal information you provide.

Eden Court Highlands is a secure site using encryption technology to safeguard your details. Encryption technology provides billions of code combinations per order transaction and prevents other internet users from accessing your personal details. Eden Court Highlands servers use Secure Socket Layers (SSL), a sophisticated encryption technology that works with Microsoft and Netscape browsers 4.0+.

**EMail and Postal Mailing Lists**

If you sign up for mailings, we will use your personal information to keep you informed about events, news and offers that we think will be of interest to you. If you have chosen to receive them, we will also use your information to provide you with email bulletins and other email alerts letting you stay up-to-date with relevant offers.  If you register an interest in particular art form(s) when you join our email list, we will store your email address together with any other information you may provide as part of the personalisation process.

**Booking Tickets and Other Transactions** ****

When you book tickets via the site, we may need to collect information about you to process the transaction and fulfil your order. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address and your credit card details. We may also use the information to process any transactions you undertake with us and for internal administration and analysis. We disclose your information to third parties only for providing the above services to you. We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that certain web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information a user supplies themself. A cookie cannot read data from your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies, however, enhance our web site performance in a number of ways including providing a secure way for us to verify your identity during your visit to our website and personalising your experience on our site making it more convenient for you. Eden Court Highlands therefore uses cookie technology to track or record information about visitors to our site. These cookies are 'session specific' and are not used to record personal information or to associate personal information with the use of Festival City Theatre Trust services. Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from our website. You can refuse cookies by turning them off on your web browser and and you can use the site successfully without having cookies turned on.

By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by Eden Court Highlands in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

Should you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or the ways in which we process your personal data, please contact us at Eden Court Highlands, Bishops Road, Inverness, IV3 5SA TEL: 01463 239 841
